ILGWU Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Records 5780/114
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Country Miss Enrollee Applications 2-031521-ET031, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Country Miss of Bristol 2-031521-BR141, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Country Miss of Bristol Enrollee Applications 2-031521-BR141, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Daisy Sportswear 2-040109-NY011, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Daisy Sportswear Enrollee Applications 2-040109-NY011, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Daisy Sportswear 2-040109-NY012, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Daisy Sportswear Enrollee Applications 2-040109-NY012, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Danalee1-040114-LL031, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Danalee Enrollee Applications 1-040114-LL031, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- The Red Book (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Subcontractor Directories, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Alan Garment 1-011201-WB032, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Alan Garment Enrollee Applications 1-011201-WB032, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Alan Garment 1-011201-WB031, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Alan Garment Enrollee Applications 1-011201-WB031, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Amy Togs 1-011325-WB031 Renewal, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Amy Togs Enrollee Applications 1-011325-WB031 Renewal, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Annette Fashions 1-011414-JN031, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Annette Fashions Enrollee Applications1-011414-JN031, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Annette Fashions 1-011414-JN032, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Annette Fashions Enrollee Applications 1-011414-JN032, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Aurora Undergarment 2-012118-NY011, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Aurora Undergarment Enrollee Applications 2-012118-NY011, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Betcyan 1-020520-FR041, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Betcyan Enrollee Applications 1-020520-FR041, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Barad + Company 2-020118-SA201, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Barad + Company Enrollee Applications 2-020118-SA201, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Barad + Company 2-020118-SA202, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Barad + Company Enrollee Applications 2-020118-SA202, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Barad + Company 2-020118-TH201, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Barad + Company (Thayer) 2-020118-TH204, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Barad + Company Enrollee Applications 2-020118-TH201, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Barad + Company Enrollee Applications 2-020118-TH204, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Barlyn 1-020118-NW021, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Barlyn Enrollee Applications 1-020118-NW021, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Barlyn 1-020118-NW022, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Barlyn Enrollee Applications1-020118-NW022, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Bonnell 1-021514-ML021, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Bonnell Enrollee Applications 1-021514-ML021, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Broadway Fashions 1-021815-HC021, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Broadway Fashions Enrollee Applications 1-021815-HC021, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Brockton 1-021815-BR041, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Brockton Enrollee Applications 1-021815-BR041, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Brockton 1-021815-BR042, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Brockton Enrollee Applications 1-021815-BR042, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- CM Clothing 2-031303-CK211, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- CM Clothing Enrollee Applications 2-031303-CK211, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Calvert Manufacturing 2-030112-MD012, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Calvert Manufacturing 2-030112-MD011, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Calvert Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 2-030112-MD011, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Calvert Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 2-030112-MD012, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Capitol Swinmwear1-030116-HT051, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Capitol Swimwear Enrollee Applications 1-030116-HT051, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Capitol Swimwear 1-030116-HT052, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Capitol Swimwear Enrollee Applications 1-030116-HT052, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Cata Garment 1-030120-AT031, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Cata Garment Enrollee Applications 1-030120-AT031, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Catalina 1-030120-AS031, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Catalina Enrollee Applications 1-030120-AS031, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Cedar Crest Apparel 2-030504-AT031, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Cedar Crest Apparel Enrollee Applications 2-030504-AT031, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Cedar Crest Apparel 2-030504-AT032, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Cedar Crest Apparel Enrollee Applications 2-030504-AT032, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Cedar Crest Apparel 2-030504-AT033, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Cedar Crest Apparel Enrollee Applications 2-030504-AT033, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Cedar Crest Apparel 2-030504-AT034, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Cedar Crest Apparel Enrollee Applications 2-030504-AT034, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Charland 1-030801-CH031, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Charland Enrollee Applications 1-030801-CH031, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Charland 1-030801-CH032, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Charland Enrollee Applications 1-030801-CH032, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- North Berwick Mills Invoices, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Malden Mills Invoices, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- David Stevens Manufacturing Invoices, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- KDK Trimmings and Novelty Invoice, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Employees - Travel Invoices, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Applications for Employment, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Mileage Records, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- AJTRC Invoices, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Liberty Frocks, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Clifford Manufacturing, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Duo Sportswear, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Felco Athletic Wear, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Gemini Corp, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Country Miss Glasgow, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- D. Glasgow and Sons (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Greendell Manufacturing, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Green Mountain Sportswear, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Hamilton Dress Shop, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Indiana Sportswear, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- J + R Dress Company, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Jane Martin, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- JoAnn Apparel, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Jomar Manufacturing, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Joyce Sportswear, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- KDK Trimmings and Novelty, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Kaychester, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Long Island Pattern, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Lucky Star, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Maidenform, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Mar-Lil Industries, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Nancy Dee Dresses, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- New Bedford Manufacturing, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- North Berwick Mills Summary Sheet (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Colebrook Terry, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- March Invoices, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- June Invoices, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- April Invoices, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Invoices, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- April Invoices, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- February Invoices, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- May Invoices, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- May Invoices, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- July Invoices, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- May Invoices, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- DOL-ETA General, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- DOL-ETA General, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Weekly Invoice Forms, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- DOL-ETA Contracts, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- AJTRC Employee Profiles and Salaries, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Subcontractors Enrollee Applications, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Subcontractor Payroll Records, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Subcontractor Payroll Records, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- AJTRC Completed Programs, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Building Lease, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Address Books (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Flyers Describing Program, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Suspended Subcontracts, 1979-1981 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Applications Sent, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Applications Approved for Contract, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Applications, Approved but Hold (No Work), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Applications, Approved but Hold (Other Reasons), 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Cancelled Contracts, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Applications, Pending (Waiting to Hear from Firm), 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Applications, Rejected (Other Reasons), 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Applications, Rejected (Low Earnings), 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Applications, Rejected (Wages Below Minimum), 1980 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Brochures (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Atlantic Apparel Association, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Ladies Apparel Association (Box 8, Folder 25)
- New England Apparel Association, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Northeast Apparel Association (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Trainees' Incentive Plans (Box 8, Folder 28)
- College Town Contractors (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Drug Program, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Major Medical Forms (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Dental Plan, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Benefit Samples (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Atlantic Apparel Study, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Government Form 5134 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Government Form 5136 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Government Form 6140 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Government Blank Report Forms (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Government EDA In-House Forms, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Missing Information Letters (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Missing Information Forms (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Reporting Guidelines for Subcontractors (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Initial Contract Letters (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Over-Time Hours and Pay (Box 9, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Contract Letters (Blanks) (Box 9, Folder 13)
- End of Contract Notices to Union (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Length of Training Memo (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Termination Form Reminder (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Enrollee Cutoff Date Memo (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Sales Tax Exemption, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Delinquent Invoices (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Reimbursement Letter (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Refusal of Reimbursement: Per Clause of Contract (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Refusal of Reimbursement for Enrollees Over Two-Week Period (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Final Payment to Subcontractor (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Forms - Approved Dismissal of Trainees (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Notice of Ineligibility Forms (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Miscellaneous CETA Information, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- ILGWU Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Inter-Office Memos, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Project Coordinator Checklist (Box 9, Folder 29)
- ILGWU Contract Letters (Completed), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- ILGWU Contract Letters (Completed), 1980 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- End of Contract Notices (Completed), 1981 (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Targeted Jobs Tax Credit, 1979-1981 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- JTR, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Franklin County, PA, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Reading, PA, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Manpower Lehigh Valley, PA, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Machine Workers Union, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- National Textile Training Program, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 39)
- State of New Jersey, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Rockwell, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Worcester Manpower Consortium, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Burlington County, NJ, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- UAW - Gary, Indiana, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Suffolk County, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Wolverine Knitting, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Council for Revitalization of Employment and Industry, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 47)
- P.R.I.D.E., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Private Industry Council of Oneida County, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Newspaper Articles, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Quarterly Summary of AJTRC, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Contract with Vyorst, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Liability (Aetna), 1979 (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Association Meeting Minutes, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- DOL Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 55)
- A Study to Evaluate Strategies for Improving the Competitiveness in the World Market Place of the US Men's Apparel Industry, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Summary of Response to Request for Proposal: Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Response to Solicitation: Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Bertrand Frank Correspondence, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Technology Development Opportunities for the American Apparel Industry, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance (Box 10, Folder 6)
- An Analysis of Success and Failure Among Representative American Producers of Men's Tailored Clothing, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Articles, 1977-1980 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Adjustment Assistance Certification Calendar for Firms, 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Apparel Industry Cell Model, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Retailer Discussion Outline, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- NYC TAAC Certification Petition Assistance, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Technological Changes in the Garment Industry Vol VII, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- P.A.C.E., 1980 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Summary of Apparel Industry Evaluation Proposal, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- P.A.C.E., 1981 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Payment Management Manual (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Analysis of Problems and Needs of the Import Impacted Segments of the Women's and Children's Apparel Manufacturing Industry, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Draft (Box 10, Folder 19)
- AJTRC Comparative Matrix of the 20 Firms (Box 10, Folder 20)
- AJTRC Matrix Draft, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- AJTRC Matrix, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- A Study to Evaluate Strategies for Improving the Competitiveness in the World Market Place of the US Men's Apparel Industry, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Report Addendum, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Progress Billing for AJTRC, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Bertrand Frank Proposal to AJTRC, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Apparel Industry Overview, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Contracts and Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- A Program to Stabilize and Revitalize the US Footwear Industry, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Technological Development Opportunities for the American Apparel Industry, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- An Analysis of Success and Failure Among Representative American Producers of Men's Tailored Clothing, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Study to Improve the Efficiency of Post-Knitting Operations in Knitted Outerwear Mills, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Analysis of Problems and Needs of the Import Impacted Segments of the Women's and Children's Apparel Manufacturing Industry, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Analysis of Problems and Needs of the Import Impacted Segments of the Women's and Children's Apparel Manufacturing Industry 2nd Draft, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Apparel Industry Overview, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Analysis of Problems and Needs of the Import Impacted Segments of the Women's and Children's Apparel Manufacturing Industry (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Weintraub Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Lester Spielman Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Finances, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Correspondence, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- DOC-EDA Check Stubs, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Reimbursement Sheets, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Correspondence, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Department of Labor Correspondence, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Barad & Co Hours (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Proposal to Assist the Apparel Job Training and Research Corporation Administer Its OJT Program Involving Selected Employer Subcontractors, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Letter of Credit: Instructions for Recipient Organizations, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Contract Information, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Department of Labor Proposal, 1978-1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Specific Vocational Preparation Estimates, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- New York Coliseum Office Building Plans (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Amalgamated Bank of New York, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Personnel Forms, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Personnel Forms, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Office and Corporate Items, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Inventory Instructions, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Inventory Sheets (Box 12, Folder 22)
- DOL-ETA Invoices, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Department of Labor, 1979-1981 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- CETA Schedule (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Letter of Credit, 1977-1981 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Reply to EDA's Amendment; Calculations, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- CETA Definitions (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Finances, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Invoices (Memo Only - No Payment Due), 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Homeopathy (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Worksheets, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Subcontractors' W2 Forms, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- AJTRC On-the-Job Training Contract (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Enrollee Termination Form (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Follow-up Form (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Final Payment to Subcontractor - Cumulative Trainee Hours (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Monthly Invoice Form (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Enrollee Input Form (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Financial Status Report, Department of Commerce (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Requests for Payment, Department of Labor (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Enrollee Application Form, Department of Labor (Box 13, Folder 16)
- W-2 Forms (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Payroll Taxes (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Payroll Taxes (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Payroll Debt Advice, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Tax Information, 1979-1981 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- DOL-ETA Insurance, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Cumulative Enrollee Hours (Box 14, Folder 1)
- New Jersey, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Apparel Job Training Payroll, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Employment Applications (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Requests for Payment, Department of Labor, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Workers Comp (State Insurance Fund), 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Unemployment Insurance, 1978-1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Disability (Crum and Forster), 1981 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Payroll, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Staff Retirement Fund Schedules, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Partners Manufacturing 1-160118-WT031, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Partners Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-160118-WT031, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Partners Manufacturing 1-160118-WT032, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Partners Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-160118-WT032, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Partners Manufacturing 1-160118-WT033, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Partners Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-160118-WT033, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Partners Manufacturing 1-160118-WT034, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Partners Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-160118-WT034, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Partners Manufacturing 1-160118-WT035, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Partners Manufacturing Enrollee Applications1-160118-WT035, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Orange County Coat 1-151801-NB011, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Orange County Coat Enrollee Applications 1-151801-NB011, 1979 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Perry Enrollee Applications 1-160518-PE031, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Perry Manufacturing 1-160518-PE032, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Perry Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-160518-PE032, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Prattville Apparel 1-161801-JK211, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Prattville Apparel Enrollee Applications 1-161801-JK211, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Prattville Apparel 1-161801-JK217, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Prattville Apparel Enrollee Applications 1-161801-JK217, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Prattville Apparel Enrollee Applications 1-161801-LN081, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Prattville Apparel 1-161801-LN086, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Prattville Apparel Enrollee Applications 1-161801-LN086, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Prattville Apparel 1-161801-PV221, 1979-1980 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Prattville Apparel Enrollee Applications 1-161801-PV221, 1980-1981 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Prattville Apparel 1-161801-PV228, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Prattville Apparel Enrollee Applications 1-161801-PV228, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Prattville Apparel 1-161801-HE081, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Prattville Apparel Enrollee Applications 1-161801-HE081, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Prattville Apparel 1-161801-HE085, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Prattville Apparel Enrollee Applications 1-161801-HE085, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Proven Dress 1-161815-NY011, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Proven Dress Enrollee Applications 1-161815-NY011, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Quote Me 2-172115-CF141, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Quote Me Enrollee Applications 2-172115-CF141, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- River Bay Coat 2-180922-NB041, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- River Bay Coat Enrollee Applications 2-180922-NB041, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Romeo Dress 1-181513-BL011, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Romeo Dress Enrollee Applications 1-181513-BL011, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Rosmar Manufacturing 1-181519-WB031, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Rosmar Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-181519-WB031, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Roxanne of New Jersey 1-181524-NP021, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Roxanne of New Jersey Enrollee Applications 1-181524-NP021, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- S + F Madewell 2-190613-PS021, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- S + F Madewell Application Forms 2-190613-PS021, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- S + J Manufacturing 1-190110-NB041, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- S + J Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-190110-NB041, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Samson Altman 1-190113-WA041, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Samson Altman Enrollee Applications 1-190113-WA041, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Sayre Lingerie 1-190125-SA031, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Sayre Lingerie Enrollee Applications 1-190125-SA031, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Siena Sportswear 1-190901-CB031, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Siena Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-190901-CB031, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Siena Sportswear Enrollee Terminations 1-190901-CB031, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Snowhite Garment 2-191415-BW111, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Snowhite Garment Enrollee Applications 2-191415-BW111, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Snowhite Garment 2-191415-MW111, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Snowhite Garment Enrollee Applications 2-191415-MW111, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Solmar Fashions 1-191512-DY031, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Solmar Fashions Enrollee Applications 1-191512-DY031, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Style Sportswear 1-192025-PT021, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Style Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-192025-PT021, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- South Shore Sportswear 1-191521-BR041, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 36)
- South Shore Sportswear Enrollee Applications 1-191521-BR041, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Sunbury 1-192114-WW061, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 38)
- Sunbury Enrollee Applications 1-192114-WW061, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 39)
- Sunbury 1-192114-WW043, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 40)
- Sunbury Enrollee Applications 1-192114-WW043, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 41)
- Sunbury 1-192114-WW064, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 42)
- Sunbury Enrollee Applications 1-192114-WW064, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 43)
- Sunbury 1-192114-WW065, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 44)
- Sunbury Enrollee Applications 1-192114-WW065, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 45)
- Sunset Manufacturing 1-192114-PT031, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 46)
- Sunset Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-192114-PT031, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 47)
- Sunset Manufacturing 1-192114-PT032, 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 48)
- Sunset Manufacturing Enrollee Applications 1-192114-PT032, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 49)
- Tailored Suits. 1-200109-NB021, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 50)
- Tailored Suits. Enrollee Applications. 1-200109-NB021., 1980 (Box 15, Folder 51)
- Tarrytown Garment Co. 2-200118-TA021., 1980-1981 (Box 15, Folder 52)